Guide to the Cornell University Board of Trustees records,1865-1991.
Cornell University Board of Trustees records, 1865-1991.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Board of Trustees records, 1865-1991.
2-5-5
Cornell University.Board of Trustees.
91.2 cubic ft.; 14.4 cubic ft.
Meeting minutes, correspondence
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes and work folders for Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meetings.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
This collection forms part of collection 2-3-74.
Minutes and work folders for Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meetings.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell UniversityExecutive Committee.--Board of Trustees.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of office of origin.
RELATED MATERIALS
Included in collection #2-3-74.
CONTAINER LIST
- Executive Committee Minutes, 1868-1918
  - October 9, 1868-October 22, 1881 (Box 1)
  - October 24, 1881-Dec. 26, 1883 (Box 2)
  - Jan. 1, 1884-Dec. 28, 1886 (Box 3)
  - Jan. 1, 1887-Dec. 20, 1888 (Box 4)
  - 1889-1890 (Box 5)
  - 1891 (Box 6)
  - 1892 (Box 7)
  - 1893-1894 (Box 8)
  - Jan. 1895-April 1896 (Box 9)
  - May 5, 1896-May 4, 1897 (Box 10)
  - May 4, 1897-May 17, 1898 (Box 11)
  - May 17, 1898-April 25, 1899 (Box 12)
  - April 25, 1899-April 25, 1900 (Box 13)
  - May 3, 1900-October 23, 1901 (Box 14)
  - October 26, 1901-Dec. 9, 1902 (Box 15)
  - Dec. 9, 1902-Jan. 19, 1904 (Box 16)
  - Jan. 20, 1904-Dec. 31, 1904 (Box 17)
  - Jan. 2, 1905-Dec. 27, 1905 (Box 18)
  - Jan. 5, 1906-Dec. 11, 1906 (Box 19)
  - Jan. 2, 1907-Dec. 30, 1907 (Box 20)
  - Jan. 14, 1908-Dec. 7, 1908 (Box 21)
  - Jan. 12, 1909-Dec. 28, 1909 (Box 22)
  - Jan. 4, 1910-June 17, 1910 (Box 23)
  - July 9, 1910-Dec. 31, 1910 (Box 24)
  - Jan. 10, 1911-Dec. 26, 1911 (Box 25)
  - Jan. 2, 1912-Dec. 17, 1912 (Box 26)
  - Jan. 13, 1913-April 29, 1913 (Box 27)
  - May 13, 1913-Dec. 16, 1913 (Box 28)
  - Jan. 6, 1914-Dec. 25, 1914 and undated pre 1914 (Box 29)
  - Jan. 15, 1915-Dec. 20, 1915 (Box 30)
  - Jan. 14, 1916-June 20, 1916 (Box 31)
  - July. 17, 1916-Dec. 23, 1916 (Box 32)
  - Jan. 6, 1917-June 1917 (Box 33)
  - Sept. 15, 1917-March 9, 1918 (Box 34)
  - C.U. Committee on General Administration - Reports Morrill Nelson Land Grant Dept. of Interior 1913-1929 (Box 35)
  - 3 Volumes
    - Executive Committee Minutes 1868-1886 (Box 36)
    - Trustees Minutes 1865-1885 (Box 36)
    - C.U. Trustees- abstract of proceedings 1868-1893, 1866-1886 (Box 36)